Guide to the Duke University Living History Program records, 1973-2005 and undated UA.22.02.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Interviews, 1973-2005 and undated; 1
  - Schlesinger, James, 1987; 56
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1987 February 23 & 24 (Box 13, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0106)
      Edit Master w/TC -- Tape 3
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1987 February 23 & 24 (Box 13, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0107)
      Edit Master w/TC -- Tape 4
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1987 February 23-24 (Box 15, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0128)
      Duke University Living History Program; James Schlesinger; February 23 & 24, 1987; Dub tape 1
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1987 February 23-24 (Box 15, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0129)
      Duke University Living History Program; James Schlesinger; February 23 & 24, 1987; Dub tape 2
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1987 February 23-24 (Box 15, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0130)
      Duke University Living History Program; James Schlesinger; February 23 & 24, 1987; Dub tape 3
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1987 February 23-24 (Box 15, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0131)
      Duke University Living History Program; James Schlesinger; February 23 & 24, 1987; Dub tape 4
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1987 February 23-24 (Box 5, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0022)
      Duke University Living History; James Shlesinger; February 23 & 24, 1987; DUB - Tapes I & II A
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1987 February 23-24 (Box 5, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0023)
      Duke University Living History; James Shlesinger; February 23 & 24, 1987; DUB - Tapes I & II B
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1987 February 23-24 (Box 5, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0024)
      Duke University Living History; James Shlesinger; February 23 & 24, 1987; DUB - Tapes III & IV A
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1987 February 23-24 (Box 5, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0025)
      Duke University Living History; James Shlesinger; February 23 & 24, 1987; DUB - Tapes III & IV B
    - Transcript, 1987 (Box 27)
      see also Misinformation in Crisis Management: The Vietnam War
  - Smith and Griffis Interviews, 2006; 57
    - Original betacam-sp Video-cassette, 2006 (Box 21, Video-cassette UA.22.02.001-Bcam-0058)
      Duke University; RBMSCL; Duke Living History Collection; Smith and Griffis Interviews; Created 2006
    - Original dvd, 2006 (Box 23, Video-disc UA.22.02.0001-DVD-0001)
      Dup Master; created 2006
    - Smith, Earl, 1974 May 4; 58
      - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1974 May 4 (Box 14, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0110)
        Interview, May 4, 1974; 11 minutes; Possibly Master copy
  - Soedjatmoko, 1989 March 24; 59
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1989 March 24 (Box 13, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0108)
      Guest: Soedjatmoko; Panelists: Ralph Braibanti, Craufurd Goodwin, Malcolm Gillis; Director: Eric Leary; Length 56:00; reel 1/2
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1989 March 24 (Box 14, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0109)
      Guest: Soedjatmoko; Panelists: Ralph Braibanti, Craufurd Goodwin, Malcolm Gillis; Director: Eric Leary; Length 41:59; reel 2/2
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1989 March 24 (Box 5, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0017)
      The Living History program of duke University presents an interview with Soedjatmoko; 3/24/89; VHS duplicate
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1989 March 24 (Box 5, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0018)
    - Transcript, undated (Box 27)
    - Suchacka, Hanna, 1997 April 17; 60
      - Original betacam-sp Video-cassette, 1997 April 17 (Box 10, Video-cassette UA.22.02.001-Bcam-0044)
        Duke University Living History Program presents; A Conversation with Hanna Suchacka; Part One; former Prime Minister of Poland; April 17, 1997; Part One-1:23:43, Part two 46:00
      - Original betacam-sp Video-cassette, 1997 April 17 (Box 10, Video-cassette UA.22.02.001-Bcam-0045)
      - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1997 April 17 (Box 5, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0028)
      - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1997 April 17 (Box 5, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0029)
        Duke University Living History Program presents; A Conversation with Hanna Suchacka; Part Two; former Prime Minister of Poland; April 17, 1997; Part One-1:23:43, Part two 46:00
      - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1997 April 17 (Box 5, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0030)
      - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1997 April 17 (Box 5, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0031)
  - Urquiti, Victor, 1989 March 31; 61
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1989 March 31 (Box 14, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0111)
      Guest: victor Urquiti; Panelists: William Ascher, Gary Gereffi; Videographer: Eric Leary; Length: 53:37; reel 1/2
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1989 March 31 (Box 14, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0112)
      Guest: victor Urquiti; Panelists: William Ascher, Gary Gereffi; Videographer: Eric Leary; Length: 1:01:30; reel 2/2
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1989 March 31 (Box 5, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0014)
      The Living History program of duke University presents interview: Victor Urquiti; 3/31/89/ use copy
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1989 March 31 (Box 5, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0015)
      The Living History program of duke University presents an interview with Victor Urquiti; 3/31/89; VHS duplicate
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1989 March 31 (Box 5, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0016)
    - Transcript, undated (Box 27)
  - Vietnam: Three Perspectives, undated; 62
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 14, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0118)
      Vietnam: 3 Perspectives; Rusk, Fulbright, Bunker; made by amy Daubert
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, undated (Box 16, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0062)
      Vietnam: Three Perspectives Rusk, Bunker, Fulbright; Duke Univ. Living History Program; 30 minute VHS tape; use copy
    - Transcript, undated (Box 27)
  - Walters, Vernon, 1992 November 5; 63
    - Original betacam-sp Video-cassette, 1992 November 5 (Box 10, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Bcam-0041)
      TC In: 00:15:00; TC Out 1:14:00; Duration 1:14:14:00; 1 + 3 Walters; 2+4 Panel; Master
    - Original betacam-sp Video-cassette, 1992 November 5 (Box 10, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Bcam-0042)
      TC In: 1:16:18:22; TC Out 2:20:00:08; Duration 1:03:41:00; 1 + 3 Walters; 2+4 Panel; Master
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1992 November 5 (Box 5, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0038)
      Duke University Living History Program Presents A Conversation with Vernon Walters Former Deputy Director of the CIA; November 5 1992; Part One-1:14:14; Tape 1
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1992 November 5 (Box 16, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0039)
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1992 November 5 (Box 16, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0040)
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1992 November 5 (Box 16, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0041)
      Duke University Living History Program Presents A Conversation with Vernon Walters Former Deputy Director of the CIA; November 5 1992; Part One-1:03:41; Tape 2
    - Transcript, undated (Box 27)
  - Wiesel, Elie, 1987 September 15; 64
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1987 September 15 (Box 14, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0113)
      Elie Wiesel Lecture; Tape #1; Duke University; Page Auditorium; September 15, 1987; presented by the Living History Program
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1987 September 15 (Box 14, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0114)
      Elie Wiesel Lecture; Tape #2; Duke University; Page Auditorium; September 15, 1987; presented by the Living History Program
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 14, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0115)
      Wiesel Edit Master
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1988 May 9 (Box 5, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0021)
      Wiessel Lecture Dub; 5-9-88
  - Woodruff, Judy, 1999 November 4; 65
    - Original betacam-sp Video-cassette, 1999 November 4 (Box 22, Video-cassette UA.22.02.001-Bcam-0065)
      Living History; Judy Woodruff; 11-4-99; 1:03:00
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1999 November 4 (Box 5, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0032)
      The Duke University Living History Program Presents; A Conversation with Judy Woodruff; November 4, 1999; Duke Recording Studios; TRT 1:03:00
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1999 November 4 (Box 5, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0033)